http://www.desco.uk.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Desco (Design & Consultancy) Ltd is committed to its users’ right to privacy and the security of personal information. We take every step to ensure that any information provided to us is kept secure and confidential, and used only for the purpose for which it was provided.
Desco (Design & Consultancy) Ltd is committed to its users’ right to privacy and the security of personal information. We take every step to ensure that any information provided to us is kept secure and confidential, and used only for the purpose for which it was provided. This notice explains our data processing practices. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any other queries, then please contact us at information@desco.uk.com.
Desco (Design & Consultancy) Ltd only collects identifying data from visitors to its website who email information@desco.uk.com using the link from our contact page. Any data supplied in this way will be used for our internal purposes only and to send you the information that you have requested, and for any other purpose for which you have given your consent.
Identifying data will be treated, always, in a confidential manner and will not be disclosed to any organisation beyond the Pell Frischmann group of companies for marketing or any other purpose without your consent, unless where required by law. Any personal communication between you and Desco (Design & Consultancy) Ltd will be
treated in accordance with the data protection legislation currently enacted.
The personal information you provide remains within your control. If at any time, you have any questions on the information that we hold on you or you wish us to stop contacting you,
then simply contact us at information@desco.uk.com
Aggregate and anonymous data concerning our website visits such as browsing patterns, may be collected and shared with third parties to build up marketing profiles, aid strategic development and audit use of the website. Our website uses small text files, called cookies. Cookies are pieces of information generated by a web server and stored within the user’s computer,  or future use.
Our website uses cookies to allow us to see how it is used. The cookies cannot tell us who you are. If you are not comfortable with the use of cookies, most browsers now allow users to opt-out of using them.
Looking For More Information?
Please fill out your details below and a member of our team will be in touch.
Name*Email*
Phone*CAPTCHACommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
